# Sunny Sun, Master of Economic

Toronto, ON **(647)-834-0028** sunx7960@yorku.ca

### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Dedicated and result-oriented Analyst with experience in **business analytics**, **data modelling**, **data-Integrity validation** and **reporting**. Apart from possessing exceptional **analytical** and **problem solving** skills, Sunny is a great team player with strong communication and presentation skills.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming Language: SQL, Microsoft Visual Basic 2015, Excel VBA

Analytical Tools SAS Enterprise Miner, SAS Base, GAUSS and R language

Business Intelligence Products: **Tableau**, Microsoft Power BI, **ETL-SSIS**Databases: Microsoft SQL Server, MS Access

#### **EXPERTISE**

✓ Data Analysis

✓ Data Mining

✓ Reporting

✓ Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC)

- ✓ Business & Functional Requirement Document
- ✓ Process Workflow & Automation Analysis
- ✓ Data Warehouse Integration Testing
- ✓ Self Service Business Intelligence

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## **Contract Analyst**

EDPYPF Services Inc. Markham, Canada

Sep 2015 - Current

- Gathered requirements and assisted in writing business requirement documents.
- Process Workflow & Automation Analysis
- Processed massive data from Excel spreadsheet to MS Access database using SQL query
- Improved reporting process efficiency by 80% using VBA Automation
- Developed a prediction model for hiring volunteers; presented the results to business stakeholders
- Developed and documented user manuals and delivered user trainings to 10 users

Environment: Excel VBA, MS Access, SQL

### **Teach Assistant**

York University, Toronto, ON

Mar 2015 – Jul 2015

- Significantly improved grading efficiency by modifying existing EXCEL VBA
- Built strong relationship with students and professor by holding weekly office hours
- Provided timely & effective feedback to professors
- Developed strong organizational skills on exams and assignments
- Conducted post exam tutorial to over 120 students

Environment: SAS, SPSS, Weka, Tableau, Excel VBA

## **Business Analyst**

Academic Project, York University

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015

- Financial Econometric
- International Trade

Environment: SAS, SPSS, Weka, Tableau, Excel VBA

## **EDUCATION**

Master of Economics,
 York University

Sep 2014 – Dec 2015

Honours Bachelor of Financial & Business Economics
 York University

Sep 2010 – Jul 2014